Guide to the Freshman Year, Yale University, Records of the Faculty and Committees
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Freshman Year, Yale University, records of the faculty and committees
1906-1954
RU 794
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.75
The records consist of minutes and reports documenting the faculty and committees of the Yale Freshman Year.
Yale University. Freshman Year
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 12-C (YRG 12-C), Records of departments, offices, and programs of the Yale Freshman Year.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of minutes and reports documenting the faculty and committees of the Yale Freshman Year.
College freshmen; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Curricula; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Curricula; Yale University -- Freshmen; Yale University. Freshman Year
- Records of the Freshman Committee and the Freshman Faculty, circa 1906-1918; Accession 19ND-A-103
  - Records, circa 1906-1918 (Box 1)
- Minutes of the General Faculty, circa 1920-1953; Accession 19ND-A-104
  - Minutes
    - 1920-1927 (Box 1)
    - 1923-1953 (Box 2)
- Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Permanent Officers, 1934-1946; Accession 19ND-A-105
  - Minutes, 1934-1946 (Box 1)
- Minutes of Meetings of the Governing Board, circa 1920-1954; Accession 19ND-A-106
  - Minutes, circa 1920-1954 (Box 1)
- Report to the Chairman of the Freshman Committee, 1920; Accession 1935-A-015
  - Report, 1920 (Box 1)